MUHABAT KHAN

MERN-STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

0308-390131

muhabatkhan03@gmail.com

https://muhabatniazi.netlify.app/

multan, Punjab, Pakistan

SKILLS

Html - CSS - Javascript

Sass - Bootstrap - Tailwind -Material Ui

React JS - Vanila JS

Node JS - Express JS - MongoDB

EDUCATION

BS-IT

Institute Of Southern Punjab

2018-2022

Bachelor of Computer Science

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu



PROFILE

front-end developer with 2+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design and mobile apps in the financial industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer

upwork/fiverr

• Followed SDLC best practices within an Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Coded using HTML, CSS JavaScript, and React to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Advocated for well-tested and documented high-quality code.
- Teamed on user-centric design strategy in the translation of UX and business requirements into coded solutions.

Back-end Developer

upwork/fiverr/local-clients

2021-2023

2020-2023

- Developed web platform back-end using NodeJS ExpressJS frameworks.
- Built flexible, reusable code and libraries for future use.
- Integrated front-end elements into SSR applications rendering.
- Built APIs and data clients to consume APIs.
- Implemented robust security and data protection measures.
- Implemented features like authentications, REST APIs, and payment method integration.

